Armando Lara

COMPUTER SYSTEM ENGINEER AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Profile

Web and mobile professional developer with more than **three years** of experience. I can implement a wide variety of tools to create, develop, design and innovate amazing stuff. My greatest strength is my skill to **design graphical user interfaces**, which enables me to offer customized client solutions.

Work Experience

Angular Web Developer, Abogado Fernando Romo, Arandas

SEPTEMBER 2019 — PRESENT

Design and development of the business control system.

Graphic designer, Extinguidores de los Altos, Arandas

FEBRUARY 2018 — JANUARY 2019

Worked as a designer and printer of customized signals, signboards, printed tarps and decals.

Education

Tecnológico Mario Molina Pasquel y Henríquez Campus Arandas, Arandas, Jalisco

AUGUST 2016 — JUNE 2021

Computer System Engineering - Databases.

Achievements

Internal contest of programming

Computer System Engineer / Tecnológico Mario Molina Pasquel y Henríquez Campus Arandas, Arandas, Jalisco

SEPTEMBER 2016 — SEPTEMBER 2019

Three times winner of the internal contest of programming.

Internal competition of science and technology week

Computer System Engineer / Tecnológico Mario Molina Pasquel y Henríquez Campus Arandas, Arandas, Jalisco

JULY 2016 - JULY 2018

Two times winner of the internal competition of science and technology week.

Contact Info

Email: armandolarae97@gmail.com

Tel: 3481036143

Links

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Skills

Php
JavaScript

Css

React

Html

Typescript

Angular

React Native

Java

Flutter

Languages

Spanish

English